Received. Thank you, sir.
The target has been secured.
Our team is on the way back.
Command Center, this is Patrol Unit 00638.
We're on our way back, over. Received.
It's time.
Start with a small pawn first.
What's wrong?
Maybe it's nothing. I felt
the screen flickered a bit earlier.
[LUSO SAFE AUTOMATIC ALARM]
Madam, the alarm in the Steel Room
at Bank Asia Macau has sounded.
CPSP police also received the alarm.
Their patrol unit is heading there.
Where is their nearest patrol unit?
They left 2 minutes
ago. On the bridge.
Estimated 5 minutes. Where is our team?
Madam, Captain Wu Yaolei here.
Team Alpha is in pursuit.
Du Ping, activate S.P.A.I.S.
S.P.A.I.S. activated.
AI CCTV & PURSUIT SYSTEM
(S.P.A.I.S.) CODE NAME: "Spice Girl"
Rewind footage from 4,328 Skyeye cameras
within a 3 km radius of the bank.
Scanning for suspicious vehicles.
Skyeye trace found. Identified something.
They didn't want cash.
What do you mean? They
left empty-handed.
Madam, they were spotted on camera 120C,
exiting Liwan Circle, heading south.
Direct all nearby patrol cars
to intercept their escape route.
Understood, Madam.
Attention, all units.
The suspect's black MPV
is disguised as a taxi.
Charlie Unit 2-5.
Heading to the intersection.
Eng Street, Trigo Street and Cacilnas Street.
Bravo 6, Lychee Street intersection.
Delta 9-2, standby in
the middle of do Sul Street.
With Skyeye and Spice
Girl, they can't hide.
Block Rua do Campo route.
Access Seac Tunnel and Cemiterio Street,
block everything. Madam.
Spice Girl rejects this plan.
All units proceed to Cacilhas Street.
Prepare to intercept. Do not intercept.
Du Ping,
disable analysis and autonomous direction.
Yes, Madam.
Alpha Team 1 and 2,
eastward to Dom Belchior Cameiro Street.
Unit 3, southeast to Tomas Vieira Street.
Unit 4, north to Artilheiros Street.
Surround them on Repouso Street.
Yes, Madam.
All units, disperse.
Ready sir. Ready sir.
Wu Yaolei.
Wu Yaolei, what are you doing?
Capture them! Come on, respond!
We're on Repouso Street. No
suspicious vehicle in sight.
What do you mean not in sight?
It's visible there, are you blind?
Madam.
Can Madam see me?
Ma'am.
How are we now, sir?
Pawn's out.
Night, Knight-Rider.
THE SHADOW'S EDGE
translation by broth3rmax
Morning, can I help you, sir?
Order a cup of latte.
Larry, you lazy bum, open the door!
What?
Police.
Sure you don't want to go to the bank?
Why would I want to go there?
A paper with half of
my signature has been stolen, right?
Right?
Maybe they won't act
this quickly.
No, they want the other half.
They need the other half.
Without the other half,
all this becomes useless.
What exactly is cryptocurrency?
Money, sir. More than
500 million Hong Kong dollars.
There's no answer at JH
Digital Asset Management.
SAFE. STRONG. SOLUTION
They might be
working on it now.
Hello, Aoxing Tower security office.
This is the Judicial Police Command Center.
We suspect someone on the 4th floor
at JH Digital Asset Management
is involved in sensitive data theft.
Please don't act alone.
When will the police arrive?
What's your estimate? 5 minutes.
Understood.
3 minutes. Okay, 3 minutes.
Found it.
Whoa... there are a lot
of files. Copy everything.
Can't you transfer the money yourself?
The password for the crypto account consists
of 12 random English words.
It's 2048 to the power of 12.
That's the algorithm behind
it. You don't know anything.
Stay put.
Impossible to remember.
2 minutes.
LOADING DATA 24%...
Xin, what are you
doing? Just browsing.
Don't touch anything else.
A lot of VIP clients.
Gordon D.
What is this? A digital encryption key.
That's Duan Zhihong.
Who is that?
CEO of the largest crypto exchange in Kuala Lumpur.
He disappeared with $1.5 billion USD,
then was mysteriously
found dead in Macau.
People still think he
faked his own death.
The firewall for this digital key is
Level TAQ-LX-5.
What does it mean? One level
less than military-grade.
Why is such an important key
hidden on a lousy server like
this? I heard Duan's $1.5 billion
is still unaccounted for.
That's more than HK$10 billion.
Copy everything.
We're running out of time, Simon. It won't take long.
Xin, let's go.
One more minute. No time left.
DATA COPYING 56%...
DATA COPYING 97%...
DATA COPYING 100%
Let's go!
Duck down!
Don't look!
Police are at the entrance.
Don't panic.
What's happening upstairs?
Sorry.
Hi, can I help you? Police.
We received a report of a robbery.
The suspects just left. 4 men, early 20s.
Go, Bishop.
Quick, chase them!
Song, block them!
Don't run!
Alpha 3 has arrived.
Bravo-4 is on site.
Bravo 1 and 2, watch the lobby.
Bravo 3 and 4, block the exits.
Bravo-3 on site. Qiuguo,
assist Forensics on the 4th floor.
Yes, sir.
Stop!
Don't move!
Don't move! Don't move!
Drop the gun! Don't move!
Stop!
Don't move, drop the
gun, don't do anything stupid!
Ignore me, do your job.
Captain Wu is being
held hostage. They're heading up.
Wynn Macau.
The kids might...
Wynn, move quickly.
What are you waiting for?
Captain.
Wu Yaolei.
Fake.
Help me. Pull!
They're using parachutes.
Captain.
Send reinforcements to Wynn Macau.
Go!
Captain, the elevator's been hacked.
How did you get down?
I jumped. Jumped?
Stay there!
Wynn Macau, rooftop.
You really jumped?
Attention, all units.
Send assistance to the new target location.
Wynn Macau. Assist in the capture.
I've contacted their head of
security, Mathew Tab.
Sit down.
They're heading to the
rooftop, call for help!
Call for help!
They must have a Plan-B,
warn Tab to be cautious.
It's not that simple.
What?
What do you mean?
How could they disappear
just like that from all the cameras?
That's what they do.
You're all tangled up.
Where are they? They're at the hotel.
Xin, the police have arrived. So quickly.
The Fort route is dead. Take the Ster route.
Why did you let them run?
They didn't run, they flew.
15 seconds. Ready for
Ster. I need the location.
Searching.
Find them, quickly!
What happened? Not us.
Why are all my cameras? The Wynn CCTV
was remotely disabled.
Everyone, move quickly. Spread out, stay alert.
As long as they're here,
they can't hide their faces.
Everyone,
activate your body cameras.
Focus on any faces you encounter.
Du Ping, manually operate S.P.A.I.S.
Run facial recognition on all
images captured by body cameras.
Okay. Find them without guest entry records,
starting with area staff.
Stay off camera.
Or we're screwed.
I'm in.
Tell me where you are,
I'll handle it from here.
The king is moving.
Turn around.
Locker room, change clothes.
Excuse me, sir.
Sir!
Alpha 2 took the MCS1 elevator to the Ground Floor.
Ray. Turn around.
Move the cart to 10 o'clock.
Attention all units. The
suspects might change their disguise.
Stay focused, keep searching.
Height 175cm, slightly long hair,
black and white hooded
baseball jacket,
dark camouflage cargo pants
backpack. He's headed to the cafeteria.
Xin, you're exposed.
Feng, cover that face. Help Xin.
Yes, sir.
Song, the man who just passed.
Now.
He's not on the guest entry list. What?
There. That's him!
I'll handle this one.
Song, chase the other guy.
Sorry. Song, clean the lens.
Pursue that one. Go!
Hurry!
[MAIN KITCHEN]
Sorry.
Where is he?
The Wynn Prosperity Tree lobby is crowded.
WYNN PROSPERITY TREE
I thought the show was after 12.
If there's a system upgrade,
they test the show in the morning.
Find them, spread out!
Be alert, stay focused.
There.
They're disguising as police.
They're posing as police!
Checkmate.
Damn it! Bastard!
Bastard!
Everything's gone. 500 million!
Not a penny left!
Crypto is impossible to trace!
You useless cops!
They hacked us and
infiltrated the CCTV system.
So... Without Skyeye,
we can't tackle
crime anymore, right?
Before we had all this technology,
how did the police do their job?
It's my fault.
Next time I'll catch
them. Even if there's a next time,
they'll likely outsmart
our every move.
Then tell me...
what are we supposed to do? If
they stop now,
what's our breakthrough?
Sorry, sir. What's the status
of the cyber division?
[Don't be discouraged, it's not your fault they got away]
We've set intrusion points and code bugs,
but there's no progress
on backtracking.
To catch a cunning fox,
we need an experienced hunter.
Are you suggesting we call Wong again?
I know he was your old boss.
But now it's the era of A.I. tracking.
And they've already skinned its weaknesses.
There are many defects in
the network and CCTV equipment,
but S.P.A.I.S. is flawless. Stop
S.P.A.I.S., learn from real operations.
Do you let your phone
take charge of your tasks?
It's not about bringing a fossil!
It could improve the police's image. Captain.
I don't care if we use
a fossil or a Spice Girl.
Find them. Capture them.
Do your job.
Oh my, Guoguo,
have you ever seen Wong's file?
He's amazing.
A lot of praise.
A champion of any model of Special Operations.
A champion in hand-to-hand
combat within the police.
5 years in a row!
Skilled in firearms, surveillance,
infiltration, intelligence gathering.
He went undercover in drug cartels
and human organ trafficking syndicates.
Controlled, straightforward actions.
Expert at blending into his surroundings.
Hobbies...
Creating code calls.
It states here that one
major mistake in his career is
a personal mistake that resulted in
his partner's death.
Write which dog
pees or poops first.
Is it really him?
Hi.
Have you found it? Not yet.
Everyone else in
the field is handling big cases
and I don’t know what I’m doing.
Observing someone who’s
already retired? Patience.
Maybe the captain is watching you.
Maybe we're not ready for field duty.
I’ll get back to you later.
Practice observing an old guy like me?
Try repeating?
Why are you following me?
You’ve got the wrong person.
You don’t recognize me?
No.
Do you need something?
You’re not following me with your jacket inside out?
Can you sit somewhere else?
Sorry. It’s fine.
At 14:23, you reached your first target,
the pet shop.
So far, you’ve
been tailing me for 4 hours 17 minutes.
You changed your clothes 3 times,
and stopped 9 times to take notes.
One of your colleagues helped you on the bus.
Just looking around. Sorry.
Isn’t it true, He Qiuguo?
That expression accidentally
reveals you.
You remember me.
Uncle Wong. We haven’t
met since I was 8 years old.
I heard you joined the unit
and inherited your father's badge number.
He must be proud.
How did you know I was at the pet store earlier?
I had some clues.
First,
never throw away your notes.
Second, when walking the dog, leaving work, and taking the bus,
none of it was accurate.
The sequence of the dogs peeing and pooping was all mixed up.
Which was the sixth dog to poop?
Al Paca-paca, the poodle.
Maybe I was mistaken if I didn't pick it up.
It confuses my memory if I pick up that note.
Not bad.
You said my colleague was on the bus.
Why did you say that? Oh, I get it.
This is not a drill.
You're checking
if I'm still sharp.
The two of you followed me for 4 hours with such skill.
What made you confident?
MACAU JUDICIAL POLICE
Long time no see, Officer Wong.
This is Inspector Wu Yaolei.
Let me handle it. No.
You call yourself the police? No wonder I felt that old man touching me.
You seem proud.
So a work partner
who died on duty...
Was that your father?
Step back.
This is the footage we collected at the scene.
This video is Wynn's recording
before the hackers turned it off.
Please play the last 15 seconds.
Play it again.
Once more.
Stop!
How can you see them?
They peeked at the camera when entering.
They must have done
reconnaissance beforehand.
and knew the camera locations.
So, why did they peek?
To check if the camera was still on.
Once the camera was off,
they changed their disguise.
Isn't that right?
Xiwang.
Is the old man upset about the change in plan?
What do you think?
Go calm him down.
Adoptive dad... we're
all back safely.
Tense day, huh?
I can explain.
You nearly jeopardized everyone.
That wasn't part of the plan.
But our mission is done.
With a bonus, no less.
What bonus?
I only see mistakes!
All these years,
I've never been caught on camera.
Now I have
you useless one!
It's fine, I'll handle it.
You're useless too!
Let go.
Let us decide this time.
Let go?
Release it.
Could you tell me
what I should be afraid of now?
Besides, you wouldn't understand.
Let me tell you what you should fear.
Adoptive father.
Adoptive father, this is our fault.
For decades, not
a single photo of me.
That changed lilac , and smiles
That changed because of
you idiots. Don't be mad.
That's more than 10 billion HKD.
With this This wealth
Silent.
That tall man.
The lightning rod is changing its clothes.
Look at the monitor. Lightning Rod.
Remember its features.
This person, gritting
his teeth. Number 2, number 2.
Found the one with earrings.
Yes, that's him.
grim.
On-screen up again some
Lightning Rod 3
is not very clear. I have
a clearer picture here!
Good, very good.
Cute Face number 2, wearing a small mustache.
Got... I found Cute Face number 3.
The one crouching. He changed disguise.
How many must sop socks). assemble tribe does gale moletrienour.
Sir, I think this one
is... Cute Face number 4.
I’ve seen this coat somewhere before.
Someone gave shepherded it to him.
Everyone listen up! There's one more person.
Send everything you
find to the main screen.
Yes, sir.
Police. Police.
Sorry.
Xiwang.
You saved my life once.
I truly appreciate this life.
I don't want
anything to happen to you.
Understood?
Understood.
We are with inline with you
life or death.
I don't want to die.
I want us all to enjoy our lives.
Ms. Sun, the coffee line in the lobby,
photographed this image that afternoon.
She is very likely the fifth person at Wynn.
Do we know her identity?
Sorry sir, not yet.
At the end of the '80s,
there was an international fugitive
formerly Special Forces
known as "The Shadow".
He served in the elite assassination squad.
During the war, he disguised
to infiltrate military and political targets.
Victims were killed load intended
And he always escaped.
Later, flew here to
seek greater fortune.
He planned more than dozens of bank robberies
and evaded 3 hunters
before disappearing without a trace in 1999.
This man might be the Shadow.
Coming out of retirement.
I remember him.
What's your next move?
This photo isn't sufficient
for facial recognition.
We're planning to add manpower
for a thorough sweep.
Area?
We have several images
of his accomplice's vehicles.
All were taken in the Old Town area.
That's a large area.
I suggest a two-pronged approach.
Conduct an open sweep
for diversion,
while sending in secret surveillance teams.
Officer Wong.
There are no more secret surveillance teams.
No more?
With today's surveillance network
and A.I.,
traditional secret surveillance teams
are almost unnecessary.
Small recommendations
for field monitoring.
You should use officers
who are least conspicuous.
Preferably ones not
seen by the suspect.
Officer Wong, why don't you help us
form a temporary team?
An impromptu secret team
formed at the last minute
won't be as effective
as a comprehensive approach.
Guoguo. Stay on your course out there.
Guoguo. Stay on your path out there.
Leave the arrest to us.
Remember that.
Guguo can show off as much as he likes.
I'm just worried that showing off
might make him arrogant
and let them escape again.
How can someone so
small become a police officer?
His father was a police officer.
Doesn't he know he's just a symbolic child?
Not even a smile.
What's it to you if I'm a cop?
I earned myu Rank our police commonwealth.
Rude!
Don't forget, it was you idiots
who let them escape.
Come on, I'm the suspect. Arrest me. Come on!
the field agent
Come on! Arrest him.
In a place like the detective unit, people
might respect you with a small fight.
They will protect you out there.
In this place, no one believes
a woman can be
the first to breach the door.
The first can also get shot.
So what?
I'm not afraid to die. But
they don't want you to die.
My life isn't their business.
They really care
about the lives of colleagues.
No one considers me a colleague.
Old friend...
Guoguo has grown up.
He's just like you.
But I know he's not happy with the unit.
Someone who gets angry easily
can cause himself trouble
while on duty in the field.
Don't move! Police!
Don't worry. I'll take care of him.
I will do it.
I'll train the undercover team.
Let's catch him.
How considerate of Captain
Wu to send so many.
Thank you. Goodbye.
You look like a policeman.
Thank you.
We're dealing with an old fox.
An ancient thief. That's why
I'm going to train you
to become ancient hunters.
Let's go.
During surveillance,
develop the instinct
to observe and remember.
A glance is all you get.
Focus on key points.
Remember distinctive and permanent features.
I'm holding my hip.
Which two fingers are in my belt?
Left index. Right middle finger.
One surveillance team is an entity.
It needs every member
to complete one mission.
Let's move out.
Guoguo.
Come in.
Starting today, you must sop up into this city.
So theory becomes defaulted to action.
Doghead calls inline Animal Paradise.
Officer Wong,
what did you say? Doghead.
Econ accord....Hath Arth. That mentions.
Unit Amity on location.
MONITORING DAY 01
I'll give alias you pipeline.
Liu, you're Al Paca-paca.
Can I ask for another name?
I'll shorten it. Alpaca.
Alright.
Wanwan... you're Tofu.
Yang Zhiwei... Rice Noodles.
Ting... Pudding.
Sun Xu... Potsticker.
Liao Qihang... Eggy.
Qiao Weidong... Lucky.
Song Keyu...
Fat Bun.
Isn't that teasing on body
shape? That's local specialty.
This is the food squad.
Better than my old unit.
He Qiuguo...
Little Flower Pinky.
Can I change it? Remove the "Little."
Then also remove "Flower."
Be patient.
You are my secret weapon.
It's like I trust you.
It's okay.
I'm used to being on the bench.
Boss, how much is this?
Where did you get this? Not your
business. Pay him and send him away.
Hey...
Don't stare at them like they're suspects.
Pull over.
Are you really here?
You've been to the same place
three times
wearing the same clothes using the
same hand and way to drink.
Your drink
is always the same amount. I'm
worried you'll need to pee.
Dehydration can also kill you.
Drink.
SURVEILLANCE DAY 03
SURVEILLANCE DAY 12
There's 10 billion at stake.
Once we get it,
we're set for life.
It's just this once.
That's what you all think, isn't it?
Money isn't everything.
Freedom is everything.
Different times,
different games.
If I let you plan
the next mission...
Do you understand what you're doing?
Simon!
Dad!
Dad! Xiwang!
You've grown up. Come here, come here.
Thank you, Dad.
Dad will be going away for a while.
Take care of your siblings.
I'll come back to you all.
Duan holds crypto
worth 1.5 billion USD.
The server location has been found.
We've got the decryption key,
but the digital vault is hard to access.
Simon is hiding in the orphanage,
making plans now.
A good place to hide.
It holds a lot of memories.
I know you're all
tired, but stay focused.
Don't want coffee? Go buy some.
Do I look tired to you?
Have you ever wondered
about killing me?
Then you could share my part.
How could we, Foster Dad?
Besides, I'm already old.
I'm just a hindrance to you.
Right?
Why did you say
I'm your secret weapon?
Are you gaslighting me? (manipulating me)
Gas what?
If anyone intended
to do that, I'd kill them.
The knife's already in your hand.
You think I didn't see that?
Am I less skilled? You think
I need special treatment too?
No, you have no issues.
You don't need special treatment.
When there's a knife in your hand...
don't blink.
Be firm,
or the shave won't be clean.
So why is everyone on the field
and I'm sitting here bringing you coffee?
Do you want to... Yes.
I do want to.
But I need you here right now.
Be my monitoring partner.
That's an order.
Yes, sir.
Bro,
if Xin hadn't held the old man back,
he could have stabbed me.
He really intended to kill me.
Is it really that good?
Just some lunch meat with egg noodles.
Is your food better than a restaurant's?
When I was your age,
all I thought about was
how to stay alive on the battlefield.
I envy you all
who can dream of anything
and dare to dream of anything.
All I want is a peaceful life
with all my brothers.
Not scattered like now.
Over the years, to protect me,
You sacrificed your time
with your brothers.
Since the day we met,
you protected me.
When all those police were chasing me,
I couldn't believe
a little beggar like you
would save me.
Then you risked your life
to keep that bankrupt orphanage
alive.
Without you, we'd have starved.
Eat mine too.
Of all the children,
I love you the most.
Because you're just like me.
Simon is more like you.
If so...
he could be very dangerous.
Eggy and Tofu, your date is over.
Change clothes and head to Point E.
Pudding. Change clothes.
Point B.
Fat Bun, Point A.
Something feels
off lately.
Stay away for a while.
I can take care of myself.
MONITORING DAY 12
MONITORING DAY 15
Return to the car. Call the police.
I'm the police.
Help!
Hey, leave them alone!
Go away!
You're quite sweet, miss.
Who are you?
Go away!
Let's go.
Move!
System shutdown.
Are you aware you're on a mission?
Protecting civilians is a police
officer's duty. At the right place and time.
You're on an active mission.
What mission? Lunch Operation for Officer Wong?
Sorry, I failed the mission.
Listen carefully.
You're on a secret surveillance mission.
Don't get caught,
no matter what.
I didn't leak anything.
But you want to take your badge!
If Shadow sees that,
it's over. And where is he?
We've been roaming for weeks.
It's time for me to do real work.
This is real work!
It's only been 2 weeks.
Do you know how long
our longest mission lasted?
8 months!
I know.
8 months.
So what?
What happened?
My dad was killed because of you!
The drug dealer escaped.
You know I didn't see him
for over a year before he died?
That was my fault.
I...
You know what I did that day?
I did what you did.
Cute kid.
I have bubble balloons here.
Like bubble balloons? Yes.
Let's play inside the van, shall we?
We have lots of
toys inside. Want to?
What? Get lost. Put the kid down.
Who are you? Put the child down!
Police.
Don't move!
What's the matter? Don't move!
Let me see your badge.
Police! Don't move!
My negligence
caused your father's death.
But you saved the child.
No.
The child abductor
escaped during the commotion.
Did they find the child?
I don't know.
As police officers,
we must stay rational.
Follow discipline.
Execute orders.
Better regret
than make a mistake.
Because that's our duty.
Possible sighting of
Shadow. Rua de Oeste Market.
Blue sweater jacket
Gray pants. Wears a brown beret hat.
Maybe wearing glasses.
Everyone, change clothes!
Prepare to identify them.
All units, attention.
Shadow spotted. Monitor the market.
Gemas Unit on the way.
Alpaca, Potsticker, east.
Eggy, Tofu, west.
Lucky, Rice Roll, south.
Pudding, Fat Bun, north.
Shadow may have seen you before.
A professional like them won't forget.
They'll be alert for the second time
and become suspicious.
Maintain a 2-unit distance.
Pinky.
Identify them closely.
They haven't seen your face.
Field surveillance advice.
You must use the most inconspicuous officer
you can.
Preferably someone the suspect hasn't
seen before.
Go ahead.
Slowly.
Keep your distance.
Doghead calling Animal Paradise.
Gemas Unit on site.
Alpaca.
Approach the fruit stall in the west.
Walk slowly.
Don't rush.
Our mission is to identify the target.
Make sure Shadow doesn't escape.
Calm down. Act natural.
He's a professional.
Don't be careless.
Potsticker, exit via the east. Okay.
Fat Bun, standby near the bridge. Okay.
Pudding, don't get too close.
Keep your distance.
Alpaca. Can you identify him?
Can't do it.
Can't see his face.
Can't be certain.
We might be able to see his face.
Eggy, Shadow might have
seen you in Aoxing.
Don't turn around.
Tofu, well done.
Pinky, it's your turn now.
Be careful.
I'm going to approach him.
Pinky, you might get exposed.
I know. I have an idea.
It's definitely him.
Confirmed.
Lower your hands.
Don't move the camera.
All units, confirmed
positive identification of Shadow.
Cute Unit, change clothes and standby.
Keep your distance.
Everyone, good job.
Target has been confirmed.
All units, do not
enter the 3-block perimeter.
I repeat, do not approach the target area.
Attention, no sirens.
The target has entered the blind spot.
Lucky, it's your turn.
Potsticker, tail him.
Don't get too close.
That bastard won't get far.
Shadow is heading to Changning Apartments.
The blocks are connected inside.
There are hundreds of apartments.
If we don't get the apartment number,
we won't have another chance.
Shadow is in Block C, Unit 1.
There are no cameras inside the building.
We'll lose him in the elevator.
Pull over.
Cute Unit. They're too far.
Cute Unit, respond.
I’m too far to chase.
Potsticker, don't follow.
Eggy, don't follow.
I'll go. Pinky can follow.
I'm going in.
Top floor.
What are you doing? Will you listen to your father or not?
What? Dating without my knowledge.
My friend caught you, you know.
Which floor?
I forgot something.
You two go ahead.
Dressing up now? Your dad knows
you can lose an earring
wearing those big headphones.
Seriously, don't bother me.
See this?
Kids don't listen when they grow up.
They're only good at opposing their parents.
They grow up with their own thoughts.
What can a father do?
You're open-minded.
Otherwise, they'll start
hiding things from you.
Your Aunt Kandam says
that guy looks like an alpaca.
Is that why you're
hiding him from your dad?
Who? The guy you're dating.
What's wrong if he looks like an alpaca?
Alpacas are cute.
He's actually handsome, you know?
It's been days.
Why did dad buy it?
Got camera signal. Everything's
the same once it hits the stomach.
Here.
Want some?
Check his background. Fine.
Shadow's face has been acquired.
Caught on camera.
Why did he spit it out?
The cleaner will
take care of it. See, it's fine.
Dad hopes you'll marry
into a wealthy family someday.
Ever seen wealthy in-laws
with uncultivated manners?
One rotten apple shouldn't
spoil the whole family.
Will dad act better?
Buy fresh fruit.
Dad saves money for you.
No more.
Goodbye.
So who's flirting with whom now?
None of your business, Dad.
Your temper is bad.
What does she see in you?
Keep moving.
My temper is good.
Now what? Follow me.
What's the sign? What's the deal?
Maybe she's right for me.
You're not serious, Dad.
Get the package. I'm
impressed by how nosy you are.
You bought a lot of stuff.
Police.
Close the door!
We need this apartment,
please step aside. Police business.
8th floor.
No. 802, got it.
Shadow lives in Channing's apartment.
Block C, Unit 1, No. 802. Info confirmed.
Pick it up.
What's that noise?
Popping bubble wrap?
Is this OCD?
This can't be broken.
No wonder it's torn.
Weird.
This is all wrong.
In the past, Shadow always
disappeared after missions
and stayed hidden for a while.
He's a man of principle.
This time, he broke
his own protocol.
What happened?
If I'm not mistaken,
my guess is
we've scared him.
Whatever he wants to play,
/log_series/ just go timelines consS/,log_1sS/,log_2sS/,log_dr,log_emmer/,log_stormy/./log_series/ consS/,log_consS/,log_sta/"
Finally stopped buying rotten apples?
What a coincidence.
How much is it?
$3.70. The price has gone up.
It's okay.
20 cents.
Everything is more breaking down now./e have log_emmet/,log_emmet/,log_town/.
This one. Thanks.
That stand is cheaper.
Are you kidding? They're worse.
Nothing's fresh.
I mean the fish stall behind it.
That's cheap.
You're right.
Especially since the owner's father is friendly.
10 dollars.
It's a pity
he passed AND ss_suddenly pass log_emmet/,log_emmet/, whose log_emmet/.
Heart attack.
Asthma.
Your daughter has grown court big.
Doesn't she want to move then?
Her mother left me because of my gambling habit.
After her mom died from illness,###controller log_emmet/,###controller log_emmet/.###controller log_emmet/")"###controller log_emmet/@controller log_motivate@",###controller log_emmet/."###controller log_emmet/,###controller log_emmet)###controller log_emmet;,sleep###.""/log_controller/,###controller log_emmet/.,###controller log_emmet/,/"###controller log_emmet")###controller log HOUSE marks###")###-}controller log emmet/log_emmet/log_emmet/,###log_emmet/./log_emmet".###controller log_emmet."###controller log_emmet-./###controller log_motivate///controller_tracks/log_controller/,###controller log_motivate/,###controller log_vc./log_emmet/,.###".).###controller log_motivate"`)###controller_skins//controller log_emmet/###logs/log_emmet/###logs/log_emmet/-log_emmet/log_emmet";,/###controller log_motivate/###controller log_motivate/###controller log_emmet)###controller_s";//controllers_log_emmet/log_emmet;./log_emmet/.###log_emmet-().###logs/log_emmet/"###-###log_motivate/###controller_leaks/log_emmet/,###controller_moblog_controller/motivate"//"log_emmet/###logs_log_emmet//###c/log_emmet/###controllers_log_emmet/###controllers_a_ triggers-particles_controller_emmet/log_emmet/log_emmet/./###log_emmet/,###controller/log_emmet.###controller;###log_emmet/./###log_emmet/-engagements_motivate_examples/log_emmet_controller/log_emmet/home_action_logs/log_emmet_controllers/,###controller emmet_log_motivate_s/control_log_emmet_motivate/motivate_log_emmet-
she moved in with me.
Thanks.
What are you doing?
Planning to work at a casino?
Selling fish isn't enough to pay
the bills. Offer grass carp.
See this callus?
It's from playing cards often
when I was young.
I wanted to be the God of Gamblers. I didn't know
that it was only in movies.
I thought
your calluses were from handling guns.
Never held a gun. But
held a chef's knife for 10 years.
If there's time. I'll
cook some dishes.
Stop by
and have a drink.
That's funny.
I was a chef abroad.
My teacher was from Hangzhou.
I cooked delicious West Lake vinegar fish.
How about today?
Sure.
I happen to have a bottle of Chilean wine,
perfect with that dish.
You bring the wine, I'll do the cooking.
Come in.
Please sit.
I'll put this in the fridge.
What's he doing? Checking for dust.
To know they just moved in.
You won't avoid it.
You might be a guest,
but you can't escape kitchen duties.
Show us your skills.
I can't wait.
How long have you been a chef?
More than 10 years.
Is that the knife you're using?
You're good with the knife.
I just enjoy
doing things right.
Do you have kids?
I'm alone.
A lonely old man.
This is my own cooking.
Your daughter seems smart.
The scar on her forehead...
what's it from?
Put your phone down.
Chat with our guest. Okay.
I'll go to the bathroom first.
If I had kids,
I'd also ban phones at the dining table.
Start cloning. What did you study?
Nursing.
Are you planning to be a nurse after graduation?
Maybe at a nursing home.
You're kind-hearted.
How did you get hurt like that?
This one?
Grade 5.
Fighting with a girl.
Why fight?
There was a classmate
being bullied. I couldn't just stay silent.
But I never told until now.
Does your dad know? He couldn't possibly know.
That's strange.
How so?
What did you say that she got hurt?
She fought back in 5th grade.
1 against 5.
Someone hit her with a bottle.
I never told anyone.
Not even mom.
You didn't tell her
because you didn't want her to worry.
Even your teacher thought you hit a door.
Right?
Then how does dad know?
After our divorce,
my debts
made me plenty of enemies.
Dad was worried they might harm you.
Actually...
dad was always near you.
See?
That's what a father does.
Then why didn't dad help me?
Help you?
Remember what you did to those kids?
It was a mess.
I was afraid to intervene. Praise me.
I defended someone.
You... What?
You committed a murder. You must be kidding.
Dad made me embarrassed.
How did it go?
Go ahead.
Thank you.
For what?
For protecting us.
There are things
that cannot be undone.
The only thing I can
do for your father
is watch over you.
I know you've been worried about me all this time.
You want to protect me.
But I'm grown up.
I'll be fine.
You're okay.
Bro...
if you fail,
then I'll take over next sop.
If we use your method, there's
no turning back for us.
I just want
to do something right.
They have anti-tracker.
Must be that hacker.
Don't proceed.
Did you check his background?
Yes.
Guoguo? Forget something?
There's nothing to worry about.
Maybe my worries are overblown.
Do you sense anything wrong?
I realize that
you've grown up now.
It's time to let go.
Let's follow your plan.
Okay. Do you understand what you're doing?
I understand.
That girl is not Guoguo.
What do you mean? There's something
wrong with this camera.
It's clearly not Qiuguo.
Send help to Wong. He's in danger!
The police are coming. I'm leaving.
I failed.
I'll find another way.
Hey.
Has Shadow made a move?
No, still quiet.
You were given a chance, Xiwang.
Those kids
did not tell Shadow
that he's being watched.
They know we're using
Shadow to track them,
so we won't touch him.
[Eliminate the target]
[Forcefully seize the digital safe]
[Your plan is crazy]
Killing me and creating chaos
will open the opportunity to release Shadow.
After failing this time, they'll
look for another opportunity.
[Including the US$30 million payment]
Their chance is also our opportunity.
We must eradicate this gang of robbers
once and for all.
[At that price]
[no one will open
that vault for you]
[US$50 million]
[Agreed]
72 HOURS LATER
Shadow is on the move.
Monitoring team, disperse.
Madam, it's the same taxi
as the one at Aoxing.
Sending photos to the monitoring team now.
We are on alert.
Once the suspect's location
is locked, we're ready to go in.
Target vehicle approaching our Headquarters.
Are they surrendering?
Doesn't look like it.
Wait!
Show that cabinet again.
Why is it still there?
This can't be resolved.
This is all wrong.
Zoom in, show it again.
What is that?
Looks like Wong's van was hit.
Officer Wong?
Wong, can you hear?
Wong, respond if you can hear.
Officer Wong? Officer Wong?
Officer Wong? Guoguo?
Their vehicle... broke in.
Whose vehicle?
Headquarters attacked?
Madam, what's happening?
Du Ping, ready to move
the command unit. Yes, madam.
Monitor, stay focused. Watch the target.
Watch every move of Shadow.
Officer Wong.
Someone's still alive.
Finish them.
His phone...
Destroyed.
The key to the puzzle
isn't numbers. It's positions.
They're using Braille letters.
The bubble wrap is also Braille.
Call Intelligence to decipher the message.
Find out their plan.
Get the phone, I'll intercept them. Hurry!
What is this place? Seems like
an old orphanage.
No other suspects in sight.
Use thermal heat detection
to track Shadow.
I need visual inside.
Captain!
Inside the orphanage!
Headquarters.
This is Alpaca. Can anyone hear?
Command center?
We've lost communication. Command center?
Friends, get to work!
Chop him up!
Do you know how many
police are house me Gillinger?
200.
If I run, they'll kill me.
So what did NB did you Domino?
The fool who got caught
becomes the bait.
Then I eliminate the biggest threat
in the Police Union.
That blinds the police.
Then I finish off that fool,
and cut off police ears too Parsons too.
garn me the fool in my followers.
But...
first you have to make sure
what's necessary.
You've grown sop now.
Do you understand what you're doing?
Who do you think I and pr get?
Kill him!
Phone signal is blocked.
Find a satellite phone
to call for help.
We'll buy time.
There he ps closer!
Have to kill him to get paid.
Shadow sent a message in Braille.
Bubble wrap and sudoku all in Braille.
Guoguo. Give that intel
to Madam Wang.
Guoguo!
Why did the police get here so fast?
Madam, we got this.
Foster father.
I failed.
I'll find another way.
You've been given a chance, Xiwang.
If we get caught by the police,
what would the old man do?
It's nobody's fault.
Just
carelessness and bad luck.
Simon's idea? My idea.
Still think you're not like me?
Xiwang, what are you
doing? You don't understand
how dangerous this person is.
Go!
This isn't part of the plan!
This old man has to die here
so you can be safe. Go!
This isn't part of the plan!
This is indeed my plan.
I'm helping you one last time.
You want to die?
Simon's my brother.
If he causes trouble...
it's my job to fix it.
I have no choice.
Then I'll guide you to your path.
Foster father!
Your life
also ends here.
Ready yourself!
He's a wolf.
We're the wolf pups.
He's our father.
In my next life,
I hope to be your biological son.
Take care of them.
Take care of their family.
Yes, sir.
Kandam, it's me.
Gundam. Like a robot. What do we know?
I just contacted Captain
Wu. Big explosion at the orphanage.
Shadow? Not quite sure.
But we've already
identified the attackers.
On the surface, they
are private security
for VIP clients at the casino.
But they also moonlight
as mercenaries,
taking high-risk jobs on the dark web.
Alpaca contacted Evidence
after receiving Pinky's message.
We'll soon receive
results thanks to him.
That's Gordon D.
Why are Duan's HK$10 billion
in the police station's server?
Without the decryption key, the loot
can only be stored as digital evidence.
The only way to access the crypto wallet
is by using its digital key,
activating the 12-word passphrase
entered with nanosecond precision.
They've been here.
Madam, leave this to us.
Be careful.
We've received a report of
a robbery, the robbers just left.
4 men, early 20s.
They're the SWAT guys from earlier.
The perpetrator shut down the electricity
to prevent us from remotely disabling the hacker.
They need the local network
within range to access the server.
What does that mean?
The hacker just got here.
We were wrong.
Why were we wrong?
The old man got himself
caught.
Like an idiot.
He was outsmarted by the police.
The cop's house is too
clean. Not a single router.
That's very strange.
It's impossible that the old man didn't notice.
But he's still playing along.
What are you trying to say?
I think
he actually kept
the police off our trail.
"Ghost Car" trap?
He's not that noble.
He's the most cunning,
ruthless,
and...
He's a father.
Calm down.
Run first.
Then we cry.
We lost the SWAT vehicle in
the CCTV blind spot on
Calcada do Carmo street.
The robbers are likely
to escape tonight.
Monitor every possible exit
route and all departure schedules.
Every route?
That'll take a long time. We don't have time.
What should we do now?
Activate S.P.A.I.S. restore
analysis and command authority.
Alright.
Have him study the robbers' old methods
and predict their next moves.
Also show him their
latest methods.
If possible... Madam.
Spice Girls got a clue. That fast?
Suspect vehicle disappeared
in Calcada do Carmo.
Within a 3 km radius, a black
van was caught on camera.
There's a 67% chance
the robbers switched to this van.
There's an 82% chance the robbers
are heading to Wynn Palace. Wynn? Wynn again?
I said study, not to repeat old answers.
Don't move! Hands up!
Don't move!
Put down the knife.
Put down the knife!
Put it down! Put down the knife!
Don't move!
Ting.
Shadow is still alive.
Kneel! Hands on your head!
Kneel!
Dad!
Kneel down! Hands on your head!
Kneel down!
Wynn Palace.
Take me there.
There's someone you haven't met yet.
I'll inline.
Spice Girl found a vehicle
relevant to a possible route
leading to suspicious individuals. [[BR]]]Is their identity suspicious?
No. A number of them.
Wynn has an art exhibition.
All paintings are being flown
back to Paris tonight.
Six Chinese personnel were Inline[[[ sop]]] into passenger list 2 days ago.
And on the night of the last robbery,
Wynn also had artwork left behind.
This Spice Girl is talented.
WYNN PALACE
Police. That fast?
Plan B.
Doghead here. Target X
may be in the laundry room.
Pinky, south door of the laundry room.
Golover.
Estimated time for Watch team?
Leave him to us inline; you go.
Pinky.
Target X has left the laundry room.
Little Dog and Cute Face
" inline" demonstrating their skills.
I need to talk to them.
Trying to force them
to surrender. Surrender my foot!
Attention all units. Wynn Palace
South Lawn is crowded.
Seems like there's an event tonight.
Cancel that name.
This puppy
is mad at Psycho Cat.
Pinky to Doghead.
Talk, Pinky! I'm at the party.
I think he's here,
but I can't find him. Stay calm.
Doghead to Animal Paradise.
Use Shadow's number to
call him. A.I. voice imitation?
Let the old man talk to him.
Acknowledged.
Foster dad?
Xiwang died in vain.
Tracking target X's phone now.
No anti-tracking.
He's not hiding anymore.
Pinky. Focus.
Observe people's reactions. Understood.
Simon,
the police are fishing for you.
If the police catch you today,
I'll be very disappointed.
Maybe I've already disappointed you.
You have a good plan today.
I like it.
Thank you, foster dad. But...
anyone who understands
what they're doing
will settle everything themselves.
I'll remember.
In this case,
Xiwang did a better job.
I sincerely hope you all can
live the life you want.
This is the last time I'll help you.
Shadow is deliberately stalling.
There's a chance to identify him
if he tries to move.
Pinky. Remember the key tracking points?
Look for distinctive and permanent features.
It's okay if your memory is hazy.
When you see that feature, your brain
automatically starts to help you.
I see him.
He...
Hello?
Get me out!
Madam, Pinky is not responding.
Potsticker and Tofu are at the location.
We need the characteristics of Target X.
Too many people at the party. Everyone
looks like Target X to me now.
Your Target X is 180 cm tall
weighing 68 kg.
Long hair. That's Wu Yaolei's
communication device.
He's sneaking into the VIP area.
Animal Paradise, any valid info?
Stop him.
Use my earpiece. I'll
grab another one from the car.
Report your position.
They're worried about you.
Shadow has identified
Target X. Stay calm.
He and that driver are twins.
Pinky at Animal Paradise.
Sorry for the worry.
Glad you're okay.
Find anything? The target and
that driver are twins.
VIP area, I might have found him.
Who are you? Sorry.
Shouldn't have trusted
Shadow. He has his reasons.
Everyone, report your positions.
Tofu, south entrance.
Potsticker, north entrance.
Fat Bun, north side of the dance floor.
Rice Noodle and Lucky, laundry room.
Alpaca.
Where is Alpaca?
He gave me his earpiece,
went to get another one.
No new communication device has been
activated. His badge GPS shows
he's heading to Cotai East LRT station.
He and that driver are twins!
Are you implying that...?
It no longer matters.
Fragile.
Lucky.
Calm.
Energy.
Target.
Amateur.
Family.
Shadow.
Betrayal.
Grateful. Blind.
Times have changed.
But rules remain rules.
Simon...
goodbye.
He's dead!
Madam, Officer Wong,
we captured 2
more. Without Shadow's guidance,
they have nowhere to hide.
What is the situation?
Ma'am, Officer Wong...
Liu Jinxiao. His vein was cut.
Guoguo, apply pressure to the wound.
Don't let him move.
Black hat, dark blue jacket,
black jeans. Jinxiao!
Jinxiao, don't fall asleep!
Ambulance!
I understand your feelings,
but another unit has been assigned
to follow up.
We have a new task now.
In that case, I'll take a leave.
I need a break, personal reasons.
What are you doing here?
Wu sent this order
to accompany someone on leave.
Eat up.
Thank you.
What's the status? No leads.
It's as if Shadow vanished into thin air.
Money.
Always leaves a trail,
especially in cases like this.
This is where the victim's crypto
was first transferred.
The kids claimed only 2
people knew the password.
One of them is dead.
And the money wasn't moved, right?
Not a single cent.
Do you remember what
I said about the type of thief
Shadow might be?
Old-fashioned people. Traditional.
I don't know anything about this,
and I suspect
he doesn't either. He's
still a man of his time.
What do you think he'll do?
He doesn't know how to unload crypto.
Fu is an old-school thief. His old method
was robbing jewelry stores
and forcing victims
to buy back the stolen goods
to avoid trouble and
deal with the receiver.
That's all he knows.
Let's eat. No time.
Let's go.
Why not use the door?
Sophia, where are you?
Where's my milk?
It's been days.
Did I misunderstand?
Trust your instincts.
Blame me if I'm wrong.
That's indeed my plan.
I've been thinking over the past few days.
Carrying out missions is our duty.
But having blood, emotions,
and a heart...
That's our nature.
Being a cop shouldn't
take that away.
So, back then...
you didn't do anything wrong.
Police.
Everyone out.
I know you want to make up a story,
but don't make yourself an accomplice.
Fu demanded 10 million cash
from Wang for the account password.
Meeting at Tin Seng Tea
House. I'll inform Captain Wu.
Don't act before we get there.
Wu, your ETA? 10 minutes.
Officer Wong. Less than 5 minutes.
We've tapped Qiuguo's phone.
Understood. Understood.
Sound check. Clear.
Wang is 10 minutes late.
He could leave at any moment.
He's about to leave.
Hey. Next time use the front door.
It's a small world.
Alone?
You've got the wrong person.
Don't you know me?
We've had dinner together.
Have you forgotten me?
Do you need something?
Oh, I'm so touched.
So it's you. Uncle.
Why are you dressed like that? Your hair
scared me. I thought
you were a creepy old man
trying to hit on me.
Sorry for scaring you. Forgive me.
It's okay.
You're about to leave.
Are you planning to follow me?
Alone?
Excuse me?
What do you mean?
A few days ago, you were at Wynn.
You were with a guy.
Where is that guy now?
Dead.
Breakup?
Didn't you hear what I said?
He's dead.
Team 2. Seal Ponte Cais de
Coloane and R. Navegantes.
Team 3, go to Entre-Campos,
Cordoaria and Cheoc Van.
He was killed at the LRT station.
The guy was a cop,
just like you. You're crazy!
Stay away from me!
Go!
You managed to waste my time. Kid...
you're quite skilled.
Guoguo.
Call an ambulance! Police!
Get out of here!
Please go through the front door.
My West Lake sour fish. Do you like it?
It tastes terrible!
Drop dead!
Come with me.
Let's go!
Come on!
Guoguo!
Are you okay? The wound isn't deep.
I'll be fine.
Help is almost here.
Earpiece is in the pocket.
Guoguo... chase him!
The target is heading to the front door.
Wearing a wig and black jacket.
I'll go after him.
Pinky, he's heading north.
No CCTV in that alley.
You'll have to find him yourself.
Possible suspect sighted.
It's not Shadow after all.
The roads are so confusing,
I can't find him.
Qiuguo, stay calm.
Calm yourself.
I can't find him.
Pinky, help is almost there.
He can't be far. You can do it.
Remember the key tracking points?
He Qiuguo?
Pay attention and remember.
You only have one look.
Focus on the key spots. Alone?
Remember.
Active recall first.
Where's that guy? Gradually...
Breakup? You'll start
remembering subconsciously.
Catch him!
Hand.
Bandage.
Target spotted.
I'm chasing him. Where are you?
North alley on R. do Meio
Wu, prepare for arrest.
We've arrived.
Sir, don't take painkillers like that.
Guoguo.
You can do it.
Wait!
Qiuguo, if I set a trap
at Chapel St. Francis Xavier,
can you steer him this way?
Captain, I can't do this alone.
I need my team. I need the Surveillance Team.
Pinky, missed us?
Central, Fat Bun in position.
I'm at your 8 o'clock.
Potsticker parallel, 3 o'clock.
Eggy in position. Tofu in position shocking.
9 o'clock, next street.
Calling Animal Paradise.
Doghead is secure.
Rice Noodle at 2 o'clock.
I've studied and하시 analyzed Shadow's habits.
From this point, there are
165 possible escape routes.
17 of them reach
Chapel St. Francis Xavier.
Pudding behind you.
Lucky directly ahead of target.
Coordinates and direction to the team.
I'll keep calculating his route choices
and you'll be informed.
Doghead calling Animal Paradise.
Paws Unit on site.
Alpaca in position.
Calling Animal Paradise.
Pinky on position.
Attention, Cute Unit, Field
Chapel St. Francis Xavier
about 280 meters northwest
from current target location.
Shadow is injured. He values his life.
All he wants now is to escape.
He won't risk getting shot
to harm you.
Cute Unit. You're the hunters now.
Surround and hunt.
Don't move!
Hands above your head!
I'm fine.
I'm the police.
Fu Longsheng, you're under arrest.
Madam.
He Qiuguo.
You're the one who made this happen.
You cuff me.
What's so funny?
You're quite the fighter.
Silence!
Guoguo.
Command Center,
we have detained Fu Longsheng.
Very good.
Your father must be very proud.
Sir.
Request to join the interrogation.
Aren't you on leave?
Request to end my leave.
I really miss my job.
We will definitely need your help later.
I've already taught them
everything I know.
I want to return to my retirement.
To the hospital first!